

LANGUAGES

HINDI

ENGLISH

ABOUT ME

As an experienced Ios Developer, I have a proven track record of success in this field. I have developed and released several successful apps that have received critical acclaim. I am also wellversed in the latest trends and technologies in the Ios development industry, and I am confident that I can quickly adapt to your team's needs. In addition to my technical skills and experience, I am also a strong team player with a positive attitude.

LINKS

Linkedin:

https:/www.linkedin.com/in/sahilpuri-379632140

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth 24/02/1995

Nationality Indian

Marital status Single

SAHIL **PURI**

Ward No. 3, Nurpur Kangra, Himachal Pradesh 176202, India



+919871513763



sahilpuri245@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

LTIMINDTREE PVT LTD

Noida Oct 2021 - Apr 2023

ASM ENTERPRISE PVT LTD

Bangalore Mar 2021 - Oct 2021

UNIFY TECHNOLOGY PVT. LTD

Gurugram Nov 2019 - Feb 2021

KIWITECH

Noida Nov 2018 - Nov 2019

CHETU INDIA PVT LTD

Noida Oct 2017 - Nov 2018

SWARAN SOFT SUPPORT SOLUTION PVT. LTD

Gurgaon Jul 2016 - Sep 2017

APPORIO INFO LAB PVT LTD

Gurgaon Nov 2015 - Jun 2016

Module lead

Sr. IOS developer

Sr. IOS developer

IOS developer

IOS developer

IOS Developer

IOS Developer

EDUCATION

HPBSE

2010

CBSE

2012

INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY AND SCIENCE, **CHAUDHARY CHARAN SINGH** UNIVERSITY

Ghaziabad 2015

10th

12th

BCA

SKILLS

COCOA TOUCH	UIKIT
OBJECTIVE C	SWIFT
CORE DATA	GIT
JIRA	вьитоотн
SWIFT UI	FLUTTER

COURSES

UDEMY

Apr 2023 - Present

UDEMY

Apr 2022 - Oct 2022

Flutter

MVVM Design Pattern Swih

HOBBIES

TRAVELLING LISTENING MUSIC PLAYING INDOOR AND OUTDOOR GAMES

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

LTIMINDTREE PVT LTD

Bangalore Aug 2022 - Present

ITS

Noida Aug 2014 - Aug 2014

Spot On A- Team Award

Won thrice Spot On A- Team Award in LTIMindree..

Participated in various inter college quiz competitions.

PROJECTS

Jul 2022 - Jan 2023

AkzoNobel, Visualizer

Choosing your next wall colour has never been easier. Using the Dulux Visualizer you can play with paint ideas to find your perfect palette, with a little help from friends and family.

Jul 2022 - Jan 2023

AkzoNobel, Expert

Choosing your next wall colour has never been easier. Using the Expert you can play with paint ideas to find your perfect palette, with a little help from friends and family.

Dec 2021 - Jul 2022

AkzoNobel, ICO Apps

Our global reach means we can deliver innovative solutions, consistent product quality and effective local service anywhere in the world. Interpon powder coatings are available in a wide variety of colors, finishes and performance properties tailored to the customer's individual needs.

Mar 2021 - Oct 2021

Starkey Laboratory, Engage

Using Engage patients enrolled in a Methadone treatment program can Receive notification of appointments and clinic wide information. The Engage app provides seamless integration to the clinics Methasoft Treatment Management system.

Gurgaon Nov 2019 - Feb 2021

Airtel, Airtel Xstream

Airtel Xstream is a comprehensive video streaming app that offers a wide range of digital entertainment options including: Live TV Channels MoviesTV shows Web Series Live Sports & News Users can stream theirfavorite content from various platforms like SonyLiv, Lionsgate Play, Hoichoi, Chaupal, Eros Now, Hungama, and more, all in oneplace.

Dec 2018 - May 2019

IKEA, IKEA

The IKEA mobile app is where your inspiration comes to life. Find that cute armchair you saw at your friendis place or look through thousands of products and ideas just for you - to make your space truly your own.

May 2019 - Nov 2019

Roomz

Aiims to create an inclusive living environment that gives tenants the freedom to choose according to their budget and personal preferences.

On the other hand, we help owners to reduce their burden of finding responsible tenants.

Apr 2019 - Sep 2019

ROUTE College Football Recruit

ROUTE changes the landscape of college football recruiting by

helping athletes make better decisions about where to play. Using our data tools, athletes and parents can make data-driven decisions throughout the recruiting process and target the best-fit colleges.

Nov 2017 - May 2018

OutPost HealthCare, OutPOST

Take charge of your own health. Use video, audio or chat to access doctors, nurses, mental health professionals, wellness coaches and other healthcare providers. Any time. Anywhere. Outpost Health surrounds you with a personalized circle of care and full access to your personal health records.

Jul 2016 - Jul 2017

Freedom Desi

Freedom.Desi App enlists the help ofWi-Fi sensors to track the users in vicinity in a commercial space, log footfalls and can send out promotional offers to them. Our USP lies in connecting hyper local businesses, consumers and brands into one single retail platform.

Link - https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/freedom-desi/id1146129723?ls=1&mt=8

Dec 2015 - May 2016

Wyndham Hotels & Resorts W

Book stays at 8,900+ hotels in 80+ countries across 22 trusted brands—all at your fingertips.

With our app, you'll have access to streamlined booking, convenient in-stay features, and Wyndham Rewards member extras like managing your account, tracking your points, and discovering exclusive offers.